<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Cricket&#124;FOX SPORTS</title>
        <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket</link>
        <description>Latest sports news from Cricket&#124;FOX SPORTS</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 00:52:13 +1100</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://cyber.harvard.edu/rss/rss.html</docs>
        <language>en-au</language>

                                                <item>
                    <title>Only prayer and Phil Collins can save England from humiliation in Perth, writes Brett Geeves</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>AS we look inside the two camps at the end of Day 4, bizarrely, both teams are singing songs about the rain. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/only-prayer-and-phil-collins-can-save-england-from-humiliation-in-perth-writes-brett-geeves/news-story/c03d7341aacc52a6d1dabcfbe5882dde</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>The Ashes: Australia has one hand on Ashes urn after dominating day 4 at the WACA</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>NATHAN Lyon was pilloried for saying this Ashes series may end careers but he might prove to be Nostradamus with Australia set to reclaim the Ashes.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes-australia-have-one-hand-on-ashes-urn-after-dominating-day-4-at-the-waca/news-story/f6c150fd13056df3983d4cbf468379b5</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Ashes 2017: Australia v England third Test live scores, updates, video, start time</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ASHES THIRD TEST, Day 4 — THE end is nigh for England, who are potentially six wickets away from handing back the Ashes to a rampant Australian side.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/ashes-2017-australia-v-england-third-test-live-scores-updates-video-start-time/news-story/90c63b9a81754194596bfcd07d9935c5</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Things we learned: Stuart Broad’s horror figures, Root’s shameful stats record</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THREE Tests and six innings is a big enough sample size to accurately assess England’s compounding batting woes.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/englands-pantomime-villain-stuart-broad-registers-worstever-test-figures-to-continue-ashes-horror/news-story/e25d24f1723da93b588a162ffdac66e1</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Watch: Mitchell Starc uproots James Vince’s off stump with ‘ball of the century’</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>MOST punters believe it was the ball of the Ashes series, while some even suggested it was the best delivery this century. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/watch-mitchell-starc-uproots-james-vinces-off-stump-with-ball-of-the-century/news-story/4bfa42fd97342132d394190cd9b2c0ff</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Tim Paine justifies selection gamble, set for long-term stay as Australian wicketkeeper</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>TIM Paine looks certain to win selection for the heavy duty series in South Africa after upping the tempo of the Australian dressing room with his robust form and maturity.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/tim-paine-justifies-selection-gamble-set-for-longterm-stay-as-australian-wicketkeeper/news-story/85570c706a5f9172f5552eb258a6811d</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>History makers: England’s new ball duo James Anderson and Stuart Broad most successful ever</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THEY were hit from pillar to post on and off the field on Saturday — but James Anderson made sure that he and Stuart Broad had the last laugh.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/history-makers-englands-new-ball-duo-james-anderson-and-stuart-broad-most-successful-ever/news-story/c8109200909745e843cb228d555d9fe5</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Media Watch: How Mitchell Marsh will celebrate breakthrough century</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>HE wears more criticism than any Australian cricketer — so you can forgive Mitchell Marsh for wanting to gloat a bit after his extraordinary breakthrough Test century.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/media-watch-how-mitchell-marsh-will-react-to-taking-over-a-family-record/news-story/7f4a3de443bf93a04a472f9eae99f4d0</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Hilarious tale of Shane Warne’s failed pick-up attempts in Perth</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ACCORDING to the larrikin Triple M Ashes commentary team, it’s the first time Shane Warne has struck out on the pick-up bar scene in 18 months.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/talking-points-from-day-three-of-the-third-test-australia-vs-england/news-story/12a994b071648f57f6eec74211bacff0</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Macksville area honours the late Phillip Hughes with naming of new bridge</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>PHILLIP Hughes has been honoured with a new bridge over the Nambucca River near his rural NSW hometown to be named after the late Australian cricketer. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/macksville-area-honour-the-late-phillip-hughes-with-naming-of-new-bridge/news-story/1135d289258da6aa2a84158ec519595c</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>UK View: Ashes winning captain Michael Vaughan unloads on England’s bowling attack</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THE end. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/forme-ashes-winning-captain-michael-vaughan-unloads-on-englands-bowling-attack/news-story/89302038ae2153a2c88eb52f79981170</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>The Ashes 2017 Third Test: Aussies wary of forecasted rain as they push for series-deciding WACA win</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>MOTHER Nature, not mother country, looms as the biggest threat to Australia capturing the Ashes in Perth.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes-2017-third-test-aussies-wary-of-forecasted-rain-as-they-push-for-seriesdeciding-waca-win/news-story/68de796ba4cb9239bf1e1ef21275c252</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Case grows for Steve Smith as best Aussie batsmen since Sir Donald Bradman</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>IT’S becoming indisputable that Steve Smith is Australia’s best batsman since Bradman as he ransacked England’s Ashes attack at the WACA.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/case-grows-for-steve-smith-as-best-aussie-batsmen-since-sir-donald-bradman/news-story/fdeeda2111eea7513890d4d3beeb4f01</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Ashes 2017: Steve Smith and Mitchell Marsh plunder runs in Day 3 WACA smash-up</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>STEVE Smith reinforced his reputation as Australia’s greatest batsman since Don Bradman yet was almost upstaged by the delirious arrival of Mitchell Marsh on Saturday.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/ashes-2017-steve-smith-and-mitchell-marsh-plunder-runs-in-day-3-waca-smashup/news-story/3e108e871d458da0ea8b0ab03ca5b6bf</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Brett Geeves on Mitchell Marsh’s unbelievable, unreal, extraordinary Test century</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>LADIES and Gentleman, I give you … JACQUES MARSH!</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/brett-geeves-on-mitchell-marshs-unbelievable-unreal-extraordinary-test-century/news-story/cdc47d4c5495ae3f2da5eca17798237a</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Mitchell Marsh validates selectors’ bold call with WACA Test Century</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ONE for 346 off 90 overs.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/mitchell-marsh-validates-selectors-bold-call-with-waca-test-century/news-story/dea18c383a8411e10e8e8b02999df29d</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>WBBL: Sydney Thunder beat Melbourne Stars</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>A devastating opening partnership has lifted Sydney Thunder to a comfortable nine-wicket victory over WBBL strugglers Melbourne Stars in Sydney. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/domestic-cricket/wbbl/wbbl-sydney-thunder-beat-melbourne-stars/news-story/507e50659f3b15c32d7b0f99092be9bd</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>WBBL: Adelaide Strikers score thrilling one-run win over Melbourne Renegades</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THE Adelaide Strikers produced a thrilling last-ball, one-run WBBL victory on Saturday with captain Suzie Bates proving the hero with the ball.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/wbbl-adelaide-strikers-score-thrilling-onerun-win-over-melbourne-renegades/news-story/07fec74ec08206b8195a1b0e781c73ab</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Steve Smith statistically on another level to contemporaries, second only to The Don, ties Bradman for captain’s tons</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>STEVE Smith’s incredible feats know no bounds.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/steve-smith-is-statistically-on-another-level-to-his-contemporaries-and-second-only-to-the-don/news-story/befbd729893a6afb9206f94e4cc7b8e5</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Shaun Marsh scored century in Adelaide while wearing contact lenses for the first time</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>SHAUN Marsh had a problem with his eyesight picked up before the second Ashes Test and wore contact lenses for the first time when he made his unbeaten century at the Adelaide Oval.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/shaun-marsh-scored-century-in-adelaide-while-wearing-contact-lenses-for-the-first-time/news-story/c4bc8d87cf6ace59135033e99e1c16ba</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>England bowlers savaged by Ashes great Kevin Pietersen for tactics against Steve Smith and Australia</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ENGLAND’S bowlers have had a forgettable day at the WACA, as Steve Smith and Mitchell Marsh put them to the sword, and they copped a brutal spray from an Ashes great to boot.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/england-bowlers-savaged-by-ashes-great-kevin-pietersen-for-tactics-against-steve-smith-and-australia/news-story/9b64b041ae62bc834ff7a2676052bd45</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Ashes confidential: How Steve Smith proved his ice-cool demeanour in a high-security situation</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>STEVE Smith is officially unflappable — there is no scenario in which the Australian captain can be rattled.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/ashes-confidential-how-steve-smith-proved-his-icecool-demeanour-in-a-highsecurity-situation/news-story/7b0a1b204ef530b1e3610f791f45eaf4</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Big Bash 2017/18: Preview, fixtures, predictions, key men, overseas stars</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>WITH the summer of cricket already in full swing we’ve previewed the seventh edition of the eagerly anticipated Big Bash League. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/domestic-cricket/big-bash/big-bash-201718-preview-fixtures-predictions-key-men-overseas-stars/news-story/7509a3f7d64235d6e34783747378f298</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Joe Root shouldn’t have been made England captain, says champion offspinner Graeme Swann</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ENGLAND may have been better off resisting the urge to make Joe Root captain for the Ashes, with an England great saying he would have taken another option. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/joe-root-shouldnt-be-england-captain-says-champion-offspinner-graeme-swann/news-story/6a050e8e4691cfa07b748a3cf20ba84a</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Ashes: Aussies own tail-end battle as bowlers brutalise Poms then whack them for bonus runs</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>WE are almost exactly halfway through the Ashes and there is a clear disparity between how the two teams see the contest. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/ashes-aussies-own-tailend-battle-as-bowlers-brutalise-poms-then-whack-them-for-bonus-runs/news-story/b8dfabede750c6fdab2d3c52e61b203e</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Media watch: David Warner’s worrying form; Moeen Ali’s ‘soft, weak’ dismissal and Gilchrist’s advice</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>DAVID Warner’s up-and-down form has been queried by former Test stars, but one Australian great has got a word of advice for the misfiring Australian vice-captain.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/media-watch-moeen-ali-dismissal-was-soft-weak-gilchrists-advice-for-cricket-coaches/news-story/f5a3c148e41fef08403d810946313656</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Ashes 2017: Australia v England third Test live scores, updates, video, start time</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ASHES THIRD TEST, Day 2 — Captain Steve Smith has steered Australia to stumps and out of trouble in the third Test at the WACA after bowling England out for 403.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/follow-all-the-live-action-in-the-third-ashes-test-between-australia-and-england-scores-highlights/news-story/5e301cfaa202c5fed1d02cef19be5ce1</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Former T20 star David Hussey recalls alleged spot-fixing in a match he played in</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>FORMER Australian and T20 star batsman David Hussey remembers the uneasy feeling like it was yesterday.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/former-t20-star-david-hussey-recalls-spot-fixing-in-a-match-he-played-in/news-story/53e7d0cd2230d2dab891c6d8b4ebcab2</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Shane Warne unloads on ‘rubbish’ bowling by Stuart Broad in Perth Ashes Test</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THE heat is on England’s pantomime villain Stuart Broad to lift in the third Ashes Test amid the paceman’s ongoing ineffectual series.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/shane-warne-unloads-on-rubbish-bowling-by-stuart-broad-in-perth-ashes-test/news-story/f1e5c18cb3cdd402458086fa1391f4d4</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Brett Geeves: Mitchell Marsh looks like a player still recovering from shoulder surgery, why play him?</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>CRACKS.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/brett-geeves-mitchell-marsh-looks-like-a-player-still-recovering-from-shoulder-surgery-why-play-him/news-story/f28fd8177ee85f84018659f5c9bb29e3</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>The Ashes: Steve Smith launches rescue mission as Australia fightback at the WACA</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>HEROIC Steve Smith rescued Australia from deep trouble in Perth as England’s best performed bowler became a casualty in a gripping fight for the Ashes.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes-steve-smith-launches-rescue-mission-as-australia-fightback-at-the-waca/news-story/c4a6888d4b5683feb71455190c6130f1</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Five things: Steve Smith’s DRS woes, mental disintegration and David Warner’s sleep Jeff moment</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THERE were howls around Australia when England’s final pair came to the crease and were greeted with the typical barrage of bouncers from the Aussie pace trio.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/steve-smiths-drs-woes-continue-as-joe-root-shows-him-how-its-done/news-story/88ba15c7277b2e26cd600a7689a2432c</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>‘Ten mobile phones around their waist’: Dirk Nannes’ incredible insight in to match fixing</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>FORMER Australian fast bowler Dirk Nannes has opened up about the shady world of cricket match-fixing, claiming he reported suspicious happenings to anti-corruption officials.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/ten-mobile-phones-around-their-waist-dirk-nannes-incredible-insight-in-to-match-fixing/news-story/9f53af05535e69e014eb0ad8428ad8c9</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Father of alleged fixer: If he has done something wrong, let them hang him.</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THE father of an alleged fixer who claimed to be capable of influencing the third Ashes Test has no sympathy for his son, telling an Indian paper to “let them hang him” if he has done anything wrong.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/father-of-alleged-fixer-if-he-has-done-something-wrong-let-them-hang-him/news-story/fd38f7b211dbbc88d318afef6893098c</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Captain Kirby Short leads Brisbane Heat to first WBBL win of season</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>A CAPTAIN’S knock from Kirby Short propelled the Brisbane Heat to their first win of the Women’s Big Bash League on Friday.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/captain-kirby-short-leads-brisbane-heat-to-first-wbbl-win-of-season/news-story/2b056daaa6a7a87f6f3d74993adcf635</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Jonny Bairstow scores emotional WACA century after torrid fortnight in Australia</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>LITTLE more than a fortnight ago it appeared Jonny Bairstow had thrown England’s Ashes campaign a curve ball it could not survive in a Perth bar.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/jonny-bairstow-scores-emotional-waca-century-after-torrid-fortnight-in-australia/news-story/4712e4f075e014d2740f824350ddfc36</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>The Barmy Army has targeted Australian spinner Nathan Lyon with an ugly sledge about his family life</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>NATHAN Lyon has been the target of an ugly sledge from England’s Barmy Army fans during play on day two of the third Ashes Test at the WACA.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/the-barmy-army-has-targeted-australian-spinner-nathan-lyon-with-an-ugly-sledge-about-his-family-life/news-story/438ec0241842abcede544c98b04ff243</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Rachael Haynes has worked on mental game to find top form</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>SYDNEY Thunder vice-captain Rachael Haynes is looking forward to taking some time over Christmas when the side has a week off to reflect on what’s been an incredible 2017.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/domestic-cricket/wbbl/rachael-haynes-has-worked-on-mental-game-to-find-top-form/news-story/4f5956d5429b721df0188de20bea1d88</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Big Bash League 2017-18: Fixture, schedule, dates, teams, full squads, predictions</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>WELCOME back for another season of bash, crash and fireworks. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/big-bash-league-201718-fixture-schedule-dates-teams-full-squads-predictions/news-story/c1cf8580b69150681de3b3fad8f13c39</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Australian selectors neglected crucial skill for Perth Test, according to former Aussie star</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>AUSTRALIA’s selectors paid the price on day one in Perth for neglecting a critical component of Test cricket, according to former all-rounder Simon O’Donnell.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australian-selectors-neglected-crucial-skill-for-perth-test-according-to-former-aussie-star/news-story/b5dce6b8ff4131fa2c954b320ddf1777</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Austin Waugh one of 15 under-19 players selected in Australian squad for World Cup</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ALMOST half of Australia’s under-19 World Cup squad is from New South Wales, including the son of one of former captain Steve Waugh.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/austin-waugh-one-of-15-under19-players-selected-in-australian-squad-for-world-cup/news-story/be2d6bd0ea5b988749823773f6c18723</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Brisbane Heat star Deandra Dottin returns to field of last year’s nightmare injury</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>DEANDRA Dottin is ready to turn her house of horrors into a field of dreams.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/brisbane-heat-star-deandra-dottin-returns-to-field-of-last-years-nightmare-injury/news-story/b1c91aac2940a92309a68c968c11342b</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Media Watch: Steve Finn lifts lid on England drinking culture, Spot fixing developments from India</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>INJURED English pace bowler Steve Finn has lifted the lid on the true drinking culture in the national team’s set up.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/media-watch-steve-finn-lifts-lid-on-england-drinking-culture-spot-fixing-developments-from-india/news-story/415ee3ac929c7c676270c063a4599fed</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Mike Hussey concerned about Peter Handscomb mental state</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>PETER Handscomb will not be released to play in the Big Bash League this week as Mike Hussey questioned how the axed Australian batsman will handle his swift demise.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/mike-hussey-concerned-about-peter-handscomb-mental-state/news-story/7970537e435fc2321591c3751d936059</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>The Ashes: Dawid Malan century keeps England’s faint Ashes hopes alive at WACA</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ENGLAND defied three decades of Ashes torture in Perth to mount a stunning resurgence that has enlivened the series.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes-dawid-malan-century-keeps-englands-faint-ashes-hopes-alive-at-waca/news-story/c02440b5a75f24b921f90defd4a6142e</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Brett Geeves: The WACA has stood the test of time and it’s bloody sad it is hosting its final Ashes Test</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THERE were three things that stood out on Day 1 of this WACA Test.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/brett-geeves-the-waca-has-stood-the-test-of-time-and-its-bloody-sad-it-is-hosting-its-final-ashes-test/news-story/a9bd37a6ec8d6dfb63e2db31aec4b129</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Brett Geeves: The WACA has stood the test of time and it’s bloody sad it is hosting its final Ashes Test</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THERE were three things that stood out on Day 1 of this WACA Test.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/brett-geeves-the-waca-has-stood-the-test-of-time-and-its-bloody-sad-it-is-hosting-its-final-ashes-test/news-story/a9bd37a6ec8d6dfb63e2db31aec4b129</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Ashes confidential: The day Michael Atherton found a shark on his bed</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>GET a load of this tale from former England fast bowler Alan Mullally regarding his indifferent relationship with Atherton in the 1990s. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/ashes-confidential-the-day-michael-atherton-found-a-shark-on-his-bed/news-story/38b6194d423228f0463b3e7a03356c5a</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>What we learned: Nathan Lyon is human; never take first slip for granted and DRS is not fool proof</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>IT has taken three Tests, but England may have finally found an answer to stifle the impact of Australia’s strike weapon this series.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/watch-mitch-marsh-drops-mark-stoneman-at-first-slip/news-story/53760be43d22152896c2811d8215bd56</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>ICC has beefed up efforts with unprecedented power to stop match-fixing</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>RECENT rule changes mean the International Cricket Council has never been so well equipped to crack down on fixing, with the governing body boasting unprecedented power to seize, scrutinise and retrieve data from mobile phones.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/icc-has-beefed-up-efforts-with-unprecedented-power-to-stop-matchfixing/news-story/e32eaad93074c29ba9c55f4f74dc6102</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Burning questions: What cricket’s latest match-fixing allegations mean for Australia, the Ashes and BBL</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THE extraordinary report into match-fixing which arrived on Thursday morning (AEDT) threatened to rock the cricketing world.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/burning-questions-what-crickets-latest-matchfixing-allegations-mean-for-australia-the-ashes-and-bbl/news-story/0e529d960d388e818624e7f8b774ad0b</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>England all-rounder Ben Stokes hits seven sixes in blistering knock for Canterbury</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>BEN Stokes has scored at almost two runs a ball, but has fallen seven short of a century in a return to form in his latest appearance for New Zealand club Canterbury.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/england-allrounder-ben-stokes-hits-seven-sixes-in-blistering-knock-for-canterbury/news-story/ac5938fe163386ebecf6e8ae57b60fac</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Billy Stanlake: I wasn’t far off losing my big toe due to infection</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>BILLY Stanlake came dangerously close to suffering a career-threatening injury in pre-season with Queensland, revealing that he almost lost the big toe on his left foot due to an infection.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/billy-stanlake-i-wasnt-far-off-losing-my-big-toe-due-to-infection/news-story/e06e7e2d57b38883c87742a70c11936b</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Ashes 2017: Alastair Cook’s torrid form continues</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ALASTAIR who?</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/ashes-2017-alastair-cooks-torrid-form-continues/news-story/460a821b01b82da669fac569cd015c3a</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Cricket Australia CEO James Sutherland says there’s ‘no substance’ to allegations of Ashes match-fixing</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>CRICKET Australia chief executive James Sutherland has complete faith that the Ashes have not been compromised nor are any Australian players implicated in match-fixing activities despite an explosive report which leaked on Thursday.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/live-coverage-of-cricket-australia-ceo-james-sutherlands-press-conference-on-matchfixing-claims/news-story/3246cc757a39734ce78bfa5b36efdcf6</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Cricket reacts to Ashes spot fixing allegations; ICC downplays WACA Test concerns</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>FORMER Test cricketer Geoff Lawson has reacted with scepticism to a report that Indian bookmakers claimed to be able to fix the third Ashes Test, as the International Cricket Council said the WACA Test had not been corrupted.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/cricket-reacts-to-claims-that-former-australian-cricketer-geoff-lawson-squashes-ashes-matchfixing-claim/news-story/6536bbd3f4c6d14d4ceb2ae8eaafcefc</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Complete transcript from The Sun’s investigation into Ashes match-fixing</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p class="standfirst-content">ON the morning of the third Ashes Test in Perth, Australian cricket has been rocked by claims of match-fixing. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/complete-transcript-from-the-suns-investigation-into-ashes-matchfixing/news-story/c5180178998b8dd362ad610d47030ac8</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>From John the Bookmaker to the IPL: A timeline of match-fixing in cricket</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p class="standfirst-content">THE latest match-fixing bombshell has rocked the Ashes.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/from-john-the-bookmaker-to-the-ipl-a-timeline-of-matchfixing-in-cricket/news-story/bf6d4155dd301eb90c04b62872b08d60</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Rohit Sharma makes cricket history with spectacular ODI double century</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ROHIT Sharma became the first batsman to hit three double centuries in one-day internationals as he powered India to a 141-run win over Sri Lanka in the second match of their series on Wednesday. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/rohit-sharma-makes-cricket-history-with-spectacular-odi-double-century/news-story/2c4e2429479391a60981e37a805f55c9</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>‘I’ll fix everything’: Bookies promise millions in payouts by rigging Big Bash, IPL and Bangladesh T20 league</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>LOUNGING in the plush surroundings of a suite in Dubai’s £500-per-night Kempinski Hotel, Indian businessman Sobers Joban turned to our undercover investigators and gloated: “You want to see something magic in the Big Bash?”</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/ill-fix-everything-bookies-promise-millions-in-payouts-by-rigging-big-bash-ipl-and-bangladesh-t20-league/news-story/03b6e6e831e2d9a3af025581b8ddfdd0</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Ex-Aussie cricketer in BBL match-fixing plot</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>LOUNGING in the plush surroundings of a suite in Dubai’s $900AU-per-night Kempinski Hotel, Indian businessman Sobers Joban turned to our undercover investigators and gloated: “You want to see something magic in the Big Bash?”</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/exaussie-cricketer-in-bbl-matchfixing-plot/news-story/ed78d3c468e5041f3010372a07330ee2</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>England’s director of cricket Andrew Strauss forced to leave Ashes for family reasons</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ECB director Andrew Strauss has flown home from England’s Ashes tour after his wife was diagnosed with cancer.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/englands-director-of-cricket-andrew-strauss-forced-to-leave-ashes-for-family-reasons/news-story/bbd43381a9be50840daf96f68bf64860</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Sun investigation smashes bookies’ multi-million pound plot to rig third Ashes Test</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>CRICKET chiefs launched a probe today after <a href="https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/5133944/sun-investigation-smashes-bookies-multi-million-pound-plot-to-rig-third-ashes-test/">The Sun</a> handed over a bombshell dossier on attempts to fix the Third Ashes Test.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/sun-investigation-smashes-bookies-multimillion-pound-plot-to-rig-third-ashes-test/news-story/5059df22c31bd97e87d3b9ba841eca80</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>England name same XI to play in third Test but Jonny Bairstow and Moeen Ali swap batting spots</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ENGLAND have heeded the calls of Simon Katich, Michael Vaughan and many other pundits, rejigging their batting order by promoting Jonny Bairstow to No.6. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/england-name-same-xi-to-play-in-third-test-but-jonny-bairstow-and-moeen-ali-swap-batting-spots/news-story/0d70975bf7b67b963d7d3f8b3ad40fdf</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>England has let down coach Trevor Bayliss on and off the field, according to Ian Bell and Brett Lee</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THE pressure is heating up on Trevor Bayliss with the England head coach’s tactical prowess called into play by his own stars — but an Ashes hero believes the Australian has been badly let down by a “disgraceful” playing group who have been accused of quitting on the team.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/england-has-let-down-coach-trevor-bayliss-on-and-off-the-field-according-to-ian-bell-and-brett-lee/news-story/9c19f433d1780734f6efffe4db03be2b</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Veteran Australian spinner Brad Hogg believes Chris Gayle deserves a Big Bash League comeback</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>VETERAN Brad Hogg says the Big Bash League should open its arms to a reformed Chris Gayle after another stunning innings from the West Indian batsman.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/domestic-cricket/big-bash/veteran-australian-spinner-brad-hogg-believes-chris-gayle-deserves-a-big-bash-league-comeback/news-story/8a3624c5c0e793274437355d39f44132</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>WACA curator Matt Page on the pitch that still gives him nightmares, and what to expect from third Ashes Test</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>WACA curator Matt Page says he still has nightmares about his dud pitch from two years ago, but he’s promised a far better deck for the third Ashes Test in Perth.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/waca-curator-matt-page-on-the-pitch-that-still-gives-him-nightmares-and-what-to-expect-from-third-ashes-test/news-story/87a340056a64815e6bf41ecd586d097a</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Steve Smith: England only two bad sessions from losing the Ashes</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THE pressure is squarely on England’s shoulders going into the third Test, which the touring side must at least draw to keep the series alive.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/steve-smith-england-only-two-bad-sessions-from-losing-the-ashes/news-story/5812ce11e5dd7e1af4367ca006485182</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>How Australia’s rebuild changed in the 12 months since the horrors of Hobart, sparking an Ashes revival</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>IN only a little over 12 months, Australia’s miracle rebuild has fallen apart.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/how-australias-rebuild-changed-in-the-12-months-since-the-horrors-of-hobart-sparking-an-ashes-revival/news-story/204431e101c0f8544cef201b55653921</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Steve Smith believes Peter Handscomb will be ‘unlucky’ if he cops the axe for the WACA Test</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>MITCH Marsh has firmed to make his Test comeback after Australian captain Steve Smith indicated the team was leaning towards picking the all-rounder for the third Ashes Test, starting at the WACA on Thursday.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/live-steve-smith-and-joe-root-address-the-press-ahead-of-waca-ashes-test/news-story/360c347fc9848e3f0d3e2b5acd034101</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Australia v England, third Test Ultimate Guide: Everything you need to know about the final Ashes Test at the WACA</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>AUSTRALIA has the chance to wrap up the Ashes at the WACA Ground in Perth in the third Test starting Thursday (1:30pm AEDT).</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/australia-v-england-third-test-ultimate-guide-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-final-ashes-test-at-the-waca/news-story/6379302f7240a97d667978e598a58d60</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>The Ashes 2017-2018 third Test: Mitchell Marsh poised to replace Peter Handscombe in Perth</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>AUSTRALIA has confirmed Mitchell Marsh is poised to come into the side for Peter Handscomb for the third Test, but a final call won’t be made until the toss.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes-20172018-third-test-mitchell-marsh-poised-to-replace-peter-handscombe-in-perth/news-story/bbd4a9bf30b6f347b3e5bdf1d94a37d7</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Media Watch: Dennis Lillee says current attack one of the best, Geoff Lawson hits out at selection</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ARGUABLY Australia’s greatest fast bowler Dennis Lillee has heaped praise on the current generation of quicks, describing them as “one of the best he’s seen”.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/media-watch-dennis-lillee-says-current-attack-one-of-the-best-geoff-lawson-hits-out-at-selection/news-story/ef6da9e8f9891c9da9a6526b21188d5c</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Cricket Unfiltered: Flying cricket balls puts crowd in danger</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>COMMENT: Cricket Australia needs to address the issue of crowd safety at the Big Bash before someone suffers a serious injury.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/cricket-unfiltered-flying-cricket-balls-puts-crowd-in-danger/news-story/10f3c5221aa7e713afc3ce8efe14cb52</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Joe Root opens up on off-field incidents that have derailed England’s Ashes campaign</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>FED UP, frustrated, disappointed — the doom-laden words trip off Joe Root’s tongue. And who can blame him?</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/joe-root-opens-up-on-offfield-incidents-that-have-derailed-englands-ashes-campaign/news-story/77e3717779008df96d5754682d540321</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>UK View: James Anderson says Ben Duckett incident was non-event, reveals Steve Smith plan</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>EVERYBODY just calm down, so says England spearhead James Anderson.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/uk-view-james-anderson-says-ben-duckett-incident-was-nonevent-reveals-steve-smith-plan/news-story/0427f8880a081589d45b63142fede8ea</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Opinion: If Mitchell Marsh plays at the WACA, selectors have got things unfathomably wrong</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THERE are two types of cricket fans in this world.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/opinion-if-mitchell-marsh-plays-at-the-waca-selectors-have-got-things-unfathomably-wrong/news-story/09522d091a47a0a3194d9f9390ac937e</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Chris Gayle T20 century, Bangladesh Premier League final: World record 18 sixes</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>CHRIS Gayle has smashed a ridiculous century in the Bangladesh Premier League final, hitting 146 not out off just 69 balls - and breaking his own T20 world record with 18 sixes, a ton in itself (108 runs).</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/chris-gayle-t20-century-bangladesh-premier-league-final-world-record-18-sixes/news-story/17f0d91d97a3cc5d0a844bfe85784fdf</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Alastair Cook: ‘world has changed for English cricket since Ben Stokes incident’</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ALASTAIR Cook has admitted what the rest of the world has been thinking for weeks — that the England cricket team are slow learners.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/alastair-cook-world-has-changed-for-english-cricket-since-ben-stokes-incident/news-story/cbfb1770af6145787109c1ff25bcb5fe</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Alastair Cook hits back at critics and defends England’s attitude ahead of third Ashes Test</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>MASTER batsman Alastair Cook has hit back at those questioning his desire ahead of his 150th Test — and at the same time defended England’s culture ahead of the third Ashes Test.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/alastair-cook-hits-back-at-critics-and-defends-englands-attitude-ahead-of-third-ashes-test/news-story/52c3b1bc4ba319b9dccd6a3c512de0de</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Australia’s big wicket bounty hunter Josh Hazlewood targeting his new bunny, Joe Root</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>JOSH Hazlewood has become Australia’s big wicket bounty hunter who has once again put a target on the head of England captain Joe Root in Perth.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australias-big-wicket-bounty-hunter-josh-hazlewood-targeting-his-new-bunny-joe-root/news-story/5ce6337df0d32d6b92a281885f847701</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>England’s Ashes tour is ‘an absolute joke’</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ENGLAND’S tour down under has already seen its fair share of drama as their campaign bounces from controversy to controversy.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/englands-ashes-shambles-is-an-absolute-joke/news-story/fb3081ff3e8eeb76575405662e9c5a8a</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Mitch Marsh set to replace Peter Handscomb in third Ashes Test at the WACA</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>PETER Handscomb is set to be axed from the Australian side vying to reclaim the urn in Perth, with Mitchell Marsh to return as the all-rounder.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/mitch-marsh-set-to-replace-peter-handscomb-in-third-ashes-test-at-the-waca/news-story/f5345795cdd55493792138f52e69e21a</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Recalled all-rounder Mitch Marsh says social media trolls made him ‘feel pretty s**t’</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>MITCH Marsh returns to international cricket a more obstinate operator with bat, ball and smartphone.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/recalled-australian-allrounder-mitch-marsh-says-social-media-trolls-made-him-feel-pretty-st/news-story/871bb40ea20247efc9715122caeb5258</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Perth Scorchers defeat Sydney Sixers by massive nine wickets</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THE Perth Scorchers have made a statement of intent with a stunning nine-wicket WBBL victory over in-form champions the Sydney Sixers in Wollongong. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/domestic-cricket/wbbl/perth-scorchers-defeat-sydney-sixers-by-massive-nine-wickets/news-story/713cdd6732b11e9d7cc9349f19ff4dce</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Life gets worse for sport’s unluckiest man</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>LAST week we told you the story of the luckiest man in sport getting even luckier.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/life-gets-worse-for-sports-unluckiest-man/news-story/e0b415aacbb73e5cee842f2ce1e9d1a3</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Mitchell Marsh rejoins fast bowlers cartel after brief scare</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>WHILE Ben Duckett was tipping beer over James Anderson’s head, Australia was dealing with in-team controversies of its own.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/mitchell-marsh-rejoins-fast-bowlers-cartel-after-brief-scare/news-story/b7b4506d8a1bc4fa298236089a825844</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Mitchell Marsh confident he is the game to go big in Test arena</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>MITCHELL Marsh is confident he now has the game to succeed at the highest level but even he was a little bit surprised when he was added to Australia’s squad so soon after returning to bowling duties.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/mitchell-marsh-confident-he-is-the-game-to-go-big-in-test-arena/news-story/a2af131bd8d2f284e05c26aaec0c83af</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>The Ashes 2017: Lillee, Walters, McDermott, Gilchrist, Johnson all feature in greatest WACA Tests</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p class="standfirst-content">ENGLAND have won only one of 13 Ashes encounters at the WACA. So it should come as no surprise that a list of great Perth Australia v England Tests is heavily swayed towards the home side.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes-2017-lillee-walters-mcdermott-gilchrist-johnson-all-feature-in-greatest-waca-tests/news-story/108291b553b401cfd82a82c71bee8adb</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Brett Geeves: Cricket and drinking are inextricably linked - a point England won’t escape on this horror Ashes tour</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>“JUST hit the middle one Greevesy” says Justin Langer as I swing wildly at another Ben Edmondson thunderbolt.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/brett-geeves-when-culture-is-rotten-as-it-is-with-england-curfews-are-useless/news-story/e61da524ca69c0037cb2ae4d34b53837</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Peter Handscomb’s Ashes series is over, says Michael Slater</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>MICHAEL Slater says Peter Handscomb should be dropped because he is “gone in the head”. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/peter-handscombs-ashes-series-is-over-says-michael-slater/news-story/f7cf9914fc2b53c8289d405d3d50b051</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>David Warner and Cameron Bancroft’s relationship hits frosty low in Adelaide</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>THINGS got frosty between opening partners David Warner and Cameron Bancroft in Adelaide.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/david-warner-and-cameron-bancrofts-relationship-hits-frosty-low-in-adelaide/news-story/29843e5b4eacc1d0f7541be0820c7cda</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>The Grade Cricketer: Twos — the perfect place for cricketing frauds</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>IT was a scene like any other on a Saturday. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-grade-cricketer-twos-the-perfect-place-for-cricketing-frauds/news-story/f309af29655521f2275102419190173d</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Media Watch: James Anderson and Stuart Broad accused of undermining Joe Root</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>STUART Clark believes a lack of respect for Joe Root is sabotaging England’s Ashes campaign, while Michael Vaughan is aghast at the ‘stupidity’ of the touring side’s late-night drinkers. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/media-watch-james-anderson-and-stuart-broad-accused-of-undermining-joe-root/news-story/48824252a65806bda7aaa16b11f04ca8</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Afghanistan set to play first ever Test in India, according to BCCI</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>AFGHANISTAN will make its Test debut in 2019 when India hosts the cricketing minnows for its first five-day match since attaining full status, officials said Monday. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/afghanistan-set-to-play-first-ever-test-in-india-according-to-bcci/news-story/334e419af983796fa548c7bb0f47d28a</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Media Watch: Ben Duckett wasn’t the only England player involved in latest Ashes controversy</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>HE was the one to take the fall, but Ben Duckett wasn’t the only member of the England touring party to act out of order during a drinking session in Perth last week.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/media-watch-ben-duckett-wasnt-the-only-england-player-involved-in-latest-ashes-controversy/news-story/a21db3dfcf6e7e006c2056ff55cf521a</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Tim Paine says England’s latest off-field incident will be brought up in third Ashes Test</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ASHES tension continues to bubble ahead of the third Test, with Tim Paine rejecting claims Australia crossed the line with their sledging in Brisbane. </p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/tim-paine-says-englands-latest-offfield-incident-will-be-brought-up-in-third-ashes-test/news-story/22659d86c6a1ef2f730726a4d486de6a</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>England cricket board criticised for handling of off-field incidents</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>ENGLAND cricket director Andrew Strrauss has been called out over the inconsistencies surrounding the recent — and not-so-recent — penalties handed down to misbehaving stars.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/england-cricket-board-criticised-for-handling-of-offfield-incidents/news-story/72bc2611a87ecfe5fee13a1524dfa434</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>Aussie quick Pat Cummins reveals the chance encounter that reminded him of Ashes importance</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>AUSTRALIAN fast bowler Pat Cummins has revealed the touching moment he was forced to sit back and reflect mid-series on the importance of the Ashes, and what the Australian team means to the nation.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/australia/aussie-quick-pat-cummins-reveals-the-chance-encounter-that-reminded-him-of-ashes-importance/news-story/5afca2c0ffe0fcabb563dba83a040c75</link>
                </item>
                                                            <item>
                    <title>There’s one big problem with Shane Warne’s plan for the Aussie cricket team</title>
                    <description><![CDATA[<p>SHANE Warne has been mocked for his take on what Australia needs to change ahead of the third Ashes Test in Perth starting on Thursday.</p>]]></description>
                    <link>https://www.foxsports.com.au/cricket/the-ashes/theres-one-big-problem-with-shane-warnes-plan-for-the-aussie-cricket-team/news-story/f149b5205456b71a55d845be856c229a</link>
                </item>
                    
    </channel>
</rss>